[
  {
    "category": "Intro Into Web",
    "question": "what is the abbreviation of w3c",
    "answer_1": "World Wide Web",
    "answer_2": "Text Markup Language",
    "answer_3": "Hyper Text MarkDwon Language",
    "answer_4": "Hyper Image Markup Language",
    "right_answer": "World Wide Web"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "Is <img> Element Has Attribute href",
    "answer_1": "Yes",
    "answer_2": "No Its For Anchor Tag <a>",
    "answer_3": "All Elements Has This Attribute",
    "answer_4": "Answer 1 And 3 Is Right",
    "right_answer": "No Its For Anchor Tag <a>"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "How Can We Make Element Text Bold",
    "answer_1": "Putting It Inside <b> Tag",
    "answer_2": "Putting It Inside <strong> Tag",
    "answer_3": "Customizing It With Font-Weight Property In CSS",
    "answer_4": "All Answers Is Right",
    "right_answer": "All Answers Is Right"
  },
  {
    "category": "CSS",
    "question": "what of this charatrist exist in css3",
    "answer_1": "media query",
    "answer_2": "<!doctype html>",
    "answer_3": "<hr>",
    "answer_4": "<br>",
    "right_answer": "media query"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "What Is The Right Hierarchy For Creating Part Of Page",
    "answer_1": "<h2> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "answer_2": "<h1> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h2> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "answer_3": "<h2> Then <p> Then <h3> Then <p> Then <h1> Then <p> Then <img>",
    "answer_4": "All Solutions Is Wrong",
    "right_answer": "All Solutions Is Wrong"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "How Can We Include External Page Inside Our HTML Page",
    "answer_1": "By Using Include in HTML",
    "answer_2": "By Using Load In HTML",
    "answer_3": "By Using iFrame Tag",
    "answer_4": "All Solutions Is Wrong",
    "right_answer": "By Using iFrame Tag"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "What Is The Tag That Not Exists in HTML",
    "answer_1": "<object>",
    "answer_2": "<basefont>",
    "answer_3": "<abbr>",
    "answer_4": "All Tags Is Exists in HTML",
    "right_answer": "All Tags Is Exists in HTML"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "How We Specify Document Type Of HTML5 Page",
    "answer_1": "<DOCTYPE html>",
    "answer_2": "<DOCTYPE html5>",
    "answer_3": "<!DOCTYPE html5>",
    "answer_4": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
    "right_answer": "<!DOCTYPE html>"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "What Is The Element Thats Not Exists in HTML5 Semantics",
    "answer_1": "<article>",
    "answer_2": "<section>",
    "answer_3": "<blockquote>",
    "answer_4": "<aside>",
    "right_answer": "<blockquote>"
  },
  {
    "category": "HTML",
    "question": "In HTML Can We Use This Way To Add Attributes",
    "answer_1": "<div class='class-name'>",
    "answer_2": "<div class=class-name>",
    "answer_3": "<div class=\"class-name\">",
    "answer_4": "All Is Right",
    "right_answer": "All Is Right"
  }
]
